budgetblinds.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy | Budget Blinds

Last modified: July 11, 2018

  **Introduction**

Budget Blinds, LLC ( **"Company"** or **"We"** ) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.budgetblinds.com (our " **Website** ") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On this Website.
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website.

It does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party; or
  * any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from or on the Website.

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

**Children Under the Age of 13**

Our Website is not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Website. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on this Website or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at:

**Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It**

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (" **personal information** ");
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies.

**Information You Provide to Us.  ** The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.

I authorize Budget Blinds to contact me by phone at the number provided above, including mobile phone, text, email or mail, to give me information about products. Consent is not required as a condition of making a purchase. 

**Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.  ** As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Website, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Website.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website.
  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

**How We Use Your Information**

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Website and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To notify you about changes to our Website or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our target audiences.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We may disclose aggregated information about our users without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of Budget Blinds, LLC's assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Budget Blinds, LLC about our Website users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Budget Blinds, LLC, our customers, or others.

**Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information**

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your email address used by the Company to promote our or our affiliates’ products or services, you can opt out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data or at any other time by sending us an email stating your request to [info@budgetblinds.com](mailto:info@budgetblinds.com "info@budgetblinds.com"). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions.

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (" **NAI** ") on the NAI's website.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Website home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Website and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

**Contact Information**

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:
